Kheel Center Files and Circulation Reserve List /4012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center Files and Circulation Reserve List
1970-1982
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Martin P. Catherwood Library
Labor-Management Documentation Center
Kheel Center
/4012
4 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Consists of subject files, reports, and administrative files.
3084531
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 21, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4044: Martin P. Catherwood Library Circulation Department Reserve Reading List Additional /4049: Kheel Center Additional Office Files /4051: Kheel Center Additional Office Files /4072: Kheel Center Additional Files 4074 /4088: Kheel Center Office Files /4090: Kheel Center R. Strassberg Conservation Files /4105: Kheel Center Additional Researcher Correspondence
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives; Martin P. Catherwood Library.; Martin P. Catherwood Library Labor-Management Documentation Center.
3084531
- LMDC Office File - Correspondence (up to 1973) (Box 1)
  - A, 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AFL-CIO, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Archivists, Society of 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Archives and Libraries, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Archives and Libraries Australian National University, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Archives and Libraries Balch Institute, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Archives and Libraries Bibliographies - Labor (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - B, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - C, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Canada, Public Archives of, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Archives and Libraries - California, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Canadian Labour History, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Archives and Libraries Cornell University (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Colorado Railroad Museum, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cornell University (Memos), 1964-1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Archives and Libraries DePauw University (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - D, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - E, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Archives and Libraries Eleutherian Mills Historical Library, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - F, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Archives and Libraries Federal Records Center - New York, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Archives and Libraries Ford Motor Company, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - G, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Hansl, Eva V.B., 1962-1967 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - I, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Archives and Libraries Harvard Business School, 1908-1958 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - ILR Catherwood Library (Memos), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - ILR Publications Div. - Memos, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - ILR School - Advisory Committee, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - ILR School Directories, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - ILR School (Memos) 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - ILR School (memos) 1971 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - ILR School (Memos) 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - ILR School (memos) 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - ILR School - Staff Directories, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Archives and Libraries Illinois State Archives, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - International Association of Fire Fighters, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters Archives, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - J, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - K, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - L, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Library of Congress, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - M, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Mendelsund, Henoch, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Archives and Libraries Michigan, University of, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Microfilming Corporation of America, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Archives and Libraries Missouri University, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - N, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - National Archives and Records Service, U.S., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - National Historical Publications and Records Commission, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - New England Document Conservation Center, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Archives and Libraries New York Public Library, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Archives and Libraries New York State Library, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - O, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - P, 1960-1971 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Archives and Libraries Pennsylvania State University, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Archives and Libraries Princeton University, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Q, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - R, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Railroad Memorabilia Dealers, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - S, 1950-1973 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Smith, Hilda W., 1968 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Archives and Libraries Southwestern Archives (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - State, County, and Municpal Employees, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - State University of New York (SUNY) (General), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - T, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Archives and Libraries Tamiment Institute Library, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Archives and Libraries Trade Union Libraries, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Archives and Libraries Truman Library (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - U, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Archives and Libraries University of Texas, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Archives and Libraries Utah, University of, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - V, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - W, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Archives and Libraries Warshaw Collection of Business Americana (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Archives and Libraries Wayne State University, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Archives and Libraries Wisconsin, State Historical Society, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - X, Y, Z, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 80)
- LMDC Office File (Weeded Aug. 1978) (Box 2)
  - LMDC - Ad Hoc Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - LMDC - Budget 1972-73, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Catherwood Library, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - LMDC - Collection Description (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - LMDC - Decision File, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - LMDC - Equipment, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - LMDC - Equipment 1970 - (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - LMDC - Exhibits, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Expense and Travel - 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Expense and Travel - 1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Expense and Travel 1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - LMDC Expense and Travel - 1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - LMDC - Expense and Travel - 1969- (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Status, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Development Plans, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Actors' Equity Association (Pending), 1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Old, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - LMDC - Field Trips - Reports, 1950-1955 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - LMDC - Internal Operations, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - LMDC - Library Acquisitions List Recent Accessions (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - LMDC - Meetings of the Staff, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - LMDC - Mexican Trip, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - LMDC - Mission of the School - Planning Committee, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - LMDC - Notes from the, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Student Time Records (old), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Personnel - Oral History Transcriber Instructions (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - LMDC - Personnel - Reorganization, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - LMDC - Personnel Student Assistants, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - LMDC - Personnel - General, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Personnel - Assistant Archivists Application, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Personnel - Students, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - LMDC - Planning, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - LMDC - Publication Requests, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - LMDC - Reorganization, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - LMDC - Reports, Monthly - 4/69 - 8/71, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - LMDC - Reports, Monthly - 7/65- 3/68, 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - LMDC - Reports, Monthly - 1/51 - 6/65, 1951-1965 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - LMDC - Reprinting Agreement, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - LMDC - Thank You Letters, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Labor Historians Bulletin Arky, Louis, 1953-1958 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Labor Historians Bulletin - Articles, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Labor Historians Bulletin - Christie, Robert, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Labor Historians Bulletin Circulation, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Labor Historians Bulletin Cornell, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Labor Historians Bulletin Executive Board, 1956-1960 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Labor Historians Bulletin - General, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Labor Historians Bulletin Hall, John, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Labor Historians Bulletin - Morris, Richard, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Labor Historians Bulletin News and Notes, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - National Union Catalog of Manuscript Collections, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - National Union Catalog of Manuscript Collections (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Pamphlet Collection - ILR, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Fall/Spring 1974 (Box 3)
  - Fall 1974 A-L (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Bound
  - Spring 1974 A-L (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Fall 1974 M-Z (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Spring 1974 M-Z (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Fall 1982, Spring/Fall 1973 (Box 4)
  - Fall '82, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Fall '82, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Fall '82, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Fall '82, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Fall 1973 A-L (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Spring 1973 A-L (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Fall 1973 M-Z (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Spring 1973 M-Z (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Spring 1973 M-Z (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Spring 1973 M-Z (Box 4, Folder 8)